const data = [{
  "question": "What animal lives only in China?",
  "answer": "Panda",
  "id": '0'
},
{
  "question": "What are the largest fish on the planet?",
  "answer": "Shark",
  "id": '1'
},
{
  "question": "What is the name of a bird with a bag under its beak?",
  "answer": "Pelican",
  "id": '2'
},
{
  "question": "What does the Earth's atmosphere mainly consist of?",
  "answer": "Nitrogen",
  "id": '3'
},
{
  "question": "What flower is the symbol of England?",
  "answer": "Rose",
  "id": '4'
},
{
  "question": "What flower can be called the national symbol of Russia??",
  "answer": "Chamomile",
  "id": '5'
},
{
  "question": "What is the central part of planet Earth?",
  "answer": "Core",
  "id": '6'
},
{
  "question": "Which ocean is the deepest?",
  "answer": "Pacific",
  "id": '7'
},
{
  "question": "What is the thickest tree on Earth?",
  "answer": "Baobab",
  "id": '8'
},
{
  "question": "Which country is the smallest on Earth?",
  "answer": "Vatican",
  "id": '9'
}
]

export default data